AIMANE ELOUAZZANI

Web Developer / UX Designer Safi - Morocco

Experiences

UX Design Generalist - Freelancer

Mar 2015 - Present

My role depends on the client's project which usually revolves around:

- Leading the design process to build and deliver a wide range of deliverables
- Performing user experience research and empathizing with the users
- Producing Design Systems and UI elements.
- Working with developers on the design integrations, design specifications, data and information architecture
- Exploring alternative solutions for constraints and keeping the team focused on the users needs

UX/UI Designer - Contractor | UM6P

Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

Worked as a UX/UI Designer in the "SEP Project" for the UM6P and OCP Foundation, to create a platform that helps young students and graduates in Africa strengthen their skills and leadership by offering them guidance, mentorship, knowledge and broadening their opportunities

Education

3 years - Software Engineering

Jan 2019 - Oct 2021 1337 Khouribga - 42 Network

Specialised Technician in Information Technology

Sept 2016 - July 2018

Specialised Institut of Applied Technology - TAZA

Certifications

Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design

Oct 2021 -- Google | Coursera

Technical Support Fundamentals

Sep 2020 -- Google | Coursera

Operating Systems

Sep 2020 -- Google | Coursera

Android Developer

Apr 2018 -- Udacity | OMAC Dubai

- aelouazz.github.io
- @ aymane2020@gmail.com
- **in** aelouazz
- aelouazz

About

As a designer with a background in IT, I was first drawn to UX by the way it combines empathy and creativity. It excites me to build a solution that users can interact with and find useful.

My strengths include building

My strengths include building products that are accessible and universal.

Skills

- User Research
- Graphic Design & Illustration
- Personas & User Flows
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Information Architecture
- Data Modeling
- 3d Modeling & Rendering
- Low Level Programming
- Front End Development

Tools

Adobe Creative Suite Figma				
Miro	Trello	Unix	Terminal	
Sketchbook Pro		Git	CSS	
HTML Javascript Clang			Clang	
Blender 3D .Net Framwork				
Android Studio IT Networks				
UML	Can	va	Krita	
Design	n System	s W	WCAG 2.2	

Languages

English - Arabic - French